<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xstyle-sheet-table>
    <!--http://www.w3.org/TR/CSS21/propidx.html-->
    <property name="background-color">
        <doc>
            <![CDATA[This property sets the background color of an element, either a <color> value or the keyword 'transparent', to make the underlying colors shine through.]]>
        </doc>
    </property>
    <property name="color">
        <doc>This property describes the foreground color of an element's text content.</doc>
    </property>
    <property name="background-repeat">
        <doc>If a background image is specified, this property specifies whether the image is repeated (tiled), and how. All tiling covers the content, padding and border areas of a box.</doc>
    </property>
    <property name="visibility">
        <doc><![CDATA[The 'visibility' property specifies whether the boxes generated by an element are rendered. Invisible boxes still affect layout (set the 'display' property to 'none' to suppress box
 generation altogether)]]></doc>
    </property>
    <property name="font-weight">
        <doc>The 'font-weight' property selects the weight of the font.</doc>
    </property>
    <property name="font-style">
        <doc>The 'font-style' property selects between normal (sometimes referred to as "roman" or "upright"), italic and oblique faces within a font family.</doc>
    </property>
    <property name="font-variant">
        <doc>Another type of variation within a font family is the small-caps. In a small-caps font the lower case letters look similar to the uppercase ones, but in a smaller size and with slightly
            different proportions. The 'font-variant' property selects that font.
        </doc>
    </property>
    <property name="float">
        <doc>This property specifies whether a box should float to the left, right, or not at all. It may be set for any element, but only applies to elements that generate boxes that are not absolutely positioned. </doc>
    </property>
    <property name="empty-cells">
        <doc>In the separated borders model, this property controls the rendering of borders and backgrounds around cells that have no visible content. Empty cells and cells with the 'visibility' property set to 'hidden' are considered to have no visible content.</doc>
    </property>
    <property name="background-attachment">
        <doc>If a background image is specified, this property specifies whether it is fixed with regard to the viewport ('fixed') or scrolls along with the containing block ('scroll').</doc>
    </property>
    <property name="border-collapse">
        <doc>This property selects a table's border model. The value 'separate' selects the separated borders border model. The value 'collapse' selects the collapsing borders model. The models are described below.</doc>
    </property>
</xstyle-sheet-table>